Hi, I'm Steve krenz
嗨，我是 Steve Krenz ，
and I'd like to welcome you to learn and master guitar,
欢迎大家来到 learn and master guitar ，
I am a professional guitarist,
我是一名专业的吉他手，
I live here in Nashville Tennessee
我住在田纳西州的纳什维尔，
and I teach and play and record every day,
我每天都在教授、演奏和录音，
in this session, we're going to cover the parts of the guitar,
在这节课中，我们将讨论吉他的各个部分，
how to tune the instrument,
如何调音，
what are the names of the strings,
弦的名称是什么，
correct right and left hand technique,
正确的右手和左手技术，
how to read guitar tablature,
如何阅读吉他谱，
how to read guitar chords
如何阅读吉他和弦，
and we're going to learn first two chords.
我们将学习前两个和弦。
So in our guitar tips section,
所以在我们的吉他技巧部分，
you're also going to be talking about getting your instrument ready to play,
你还将谈论如何让你的乐器准备演奏，
setting up the action, changing the strings, those sorts of issues.
设置动作，改变琴弦，诸如此类的问题。
In every session, there will be an assignment page at the end,
在每节课的末尾，都会有一个作业页面，
that shows you clearly exactly what you need to cover for the next coming session.
清楚地告诉你下一节课需要涵盖的内容。
And in our workshop time,
在我们的 workshop 时间，
I'll practice with you
我会和你们一起练习，
over the material that you need to learn in order to move on,
你们需要学习的材料，才能继续，
are you ready to learn guitar,
你们准备好学习吉他了吗，
let's go ahead and get started.
让我们开始吧。
Okay, the first thing we want to talk about is the parts of the guitar,
好的，我们首先要谈的是吉他的组成部分，
most guitars are pretty similar in their design,
大多数吉他在设计上都很相似，
this in acoustic guitar,
在原声吉他方面，
we have the body of the guitar right here,
我们在这里有吉他的琴体，
you've got the neck right here,
这里的琴颈，
the head stock here with the tuning pegs,
这里的主板上有弦钮，
your guitar has six strings,
你的吉他有六根弦，
they're attached on this end by the tuning keys,
它们在这一端通过调音键连接，
down on this end by the bridge,
这边通过琴桥连接，
there's a lot of tension on this bridge,
琴桥上有很多张力，
you always want to make sure,
你总是想要确保，
that's attach nice and tight to your sound board of your guitar,
你的吉他音板上有一个牢固的附着物，
sometimes your guitar will have a pick guard here,
有时你的吉他会在这里有一个护板，
so it doesn't scratch up your guitar when you play,
这样当你弹奏时不会刮伤你的吉他，
these silver bars and the gold bars are frets,
这些银色的或金色的条是品丝，
we will learn an awful lot about frets
我们将学到很多关于品丝的知识，
and where to where to put your fingers on them
你的手指放在哪里，
as well as on the fret board.
以及在品丝板上。
So that's the parts of the guitar,
这就是吉他的组成部分，
the next thing we need to learn is the names of our strings.
接下来我们需要学习的是琴弦的名称。
You have six strings on a guitar,
你的吉他上有六根弦，
of course it's first through six,
当然，它是从第一根到第六根，
but they're numbered from the thinnest string,
它们是从最细的一根弦开始编号的，
which is actually the bottom one,
实际上是最下面的一根，
up through the thickest, which is the top one,
到最粗的，也就是最上面的，
so this would be the first,
所以这是第一根，
this should be the second,
这是第二根，
third,
第三根，
and so on.
诸若此类。
Now, they also have letter names that go along with them,
它们也有与之配套的字母名称，
the musical alphabet goes from A to G,
音乐字母表是从 A 到 G ，
so there's different letter names that correspond with each one of these strings
所以每个弦都有不同的字母名称，
and that's one of the first things we need to learn,
这是我们需要学习的第一件事，
so let's learn that first.
所以让我们首先学习这个。
We're going to do three strings at a time,
我们要一次演奏三根弦，
when I when we do more than three strings,
当我们一次演奏三根以上的弦时，
everybody gets confused,
每个人都会感到困惑，
so we're just gonna do three strings at a time.
所以我们一次只做三根弦。
The first string is an E,
第一根弦是 E ，
so go ahead and try and play E.
继续并演奏 E 。
Your second string is a B,
你的第二根弦是 B ，
your third string is a G,
你的第三根弦是 G ，
goes to those three, that's E B and G.
三根弦，是 E B 和 G 。
So if I asked you,
所以如果我问你，
what is the second string,
第二根弦是什么，
what would you think.
你会怎么想。
And if I said what is the first string.
如果我说第一根弦是什么。
And if I said G is on what string or which string,
如果我说 G 在哪根弦上。
what would you say.
你会怎么说。
Good, let's do the next three,
好的，让我们做下三个，
so we have E B and G,
所以我们有 E B 和 G ，
we're going to the next three,
我们要看下三个，
the fourth string is D,
第四根弦是 D ，
the fifth string is an A,
第五根弦是 A ，
and the sixth string is another E,
第六根弦是另一个 E ，
two outside ones, first string and six string are both E.
外面的两根，第一根和第六根都是 E 。
So let's put them all together,
所以让我们把它们放在一起，
are you ready?
你准备好了吗？
E B G D A and E,
E B G D A E ，D
did you get all those,
你都听懂了吗，
alright, let's try,
好的，让我们试试，
if I said to you which string,
如果我问你哪根弦，
what is the note of the fifth string,
第五根弦的音符是什么，
what would you say.
你会怎么说。
What about the second string.
那第二根弦呢？
What string is a D on?
D 在哪根弦上？
What string is an A on?
A 在哪根弦上？
Pretty good.
很不错。
Alright, now let's talk about right-hand technique,
好的，现在我们来谈谈右手技巧，
the first thing we need to talk about is our pick,
我们首先要谈的是我们的拨片，
there's all different kinds of picks that you can use,
你可以使用各种不同的拨片，
there's heavies mediums and lights,
有厚的，中等的，薄的，
different shapes and sizes,
不同的形状和大小，
I'd say the best thing to start out with is a medium pick
我想说最好的开始是中等拨片，
one of these teardrop shape ones.
这些泪珠形状的其中之一。
And how do you hold it,
你怎么持有它，
well, you put your pick in between your first finger and your thumb,
你把你的拨片放在你的食指和拇指之间，
you want to kind of make a ninety degree angle right there,
你想要在那里形成一个 90 度的角度，
between your thumb and the and the downward point of the pick,
在你的拇指和拨片下拉点之间，
now your first finger is kind of pointing out a little bit,
现在你的食指几乎指向，
almost at a 45 degree angle out underneath that pick,
以 45 度的角度指向了你所拿到的拨片下面，
you've got oh what is that about a half an inch showing
那大约半英寸是什么，
and that's about how much you need to have
这就是你需要的东西，
as far as your pick, you don't want to be up too high,
就你的拨片来说，你不想放得太高，
or out too wide on it,
或者太宽，
about half an inch
大约半英寸，
and you hold it with a good strong grip,
你用很强的力抓住它，
one more thing,
还有一件事，
we need to talk about with our right hand is bracing,
我们需要讨论用我们的右手来支撑，
what that is,
这是什么，
is as we're playing the different strings,
我们在演奏不同的琴弦时，
you're going to need your hand is going to need some place,
你需要你的手到一个位置，
that it can reference itself from,
它需要一个可以自我参照的位置，
whether it's, whether it's playing the second string,
无论它是在演奏第二根弦，
or the fourth string, or the third string,
还是第四根弦，或者第三根弦，
it's gonna get confused pretty quickly,
它很快就会变得混乱，
you'll find,
你会发现，
unless it's anchored somewhere,
除非它被固定在某个地方，
so a good place to start,
所以一个好的开始的地方，
different guitar players do it different ways,
不同的吉他演奏者以不同的方式，
but a good place to start is
但一个好的起点是，
to just put your pinky and let it touch the sound board,
把你的小指放下，让它接触到音板，
I don't really particularly care where
我不关心它在哪里，
and it doesn't have to touch hard,
它不需要用力触摸，
just needs to touch it,
只需要触摸它，
just helps your hand know where it's at
只需要帮助你的手知道它在哪里，
and what it needs to do.
它需要做什么。
All right, let's try and pick a couple of these different strings
好的，让我们试着挑选几根不同的弦，
and get some practice picking the strings.
来练习一下拨弦。
Let's do the first string,
让我们来演奏第一根弦，
you ready?
你准备好了吗？
Let's go.
我们开始。
Okay, what about the third string,
好的，那第三根弦呢，
what's the name of that third string, do you remember?
你还记得第三根弦叫什么吗？
Here we go, the third string.
我们开始，第三根弦。
Very good, the fifth string,
很好，第五根弦，
do you remember name that one?
你还记得它的名字吗？
Very good, now that's the right hand let's talk about the left hand as well.
很好，现在这是右手，我们也来谈谈左手。
Left hand, this is going to be the hand that you're going to be using to fret the different notes with.
左手，这将是你要用来处理不同音符的手。
How this works,
这是如何工作的，
as far as the guitar is concerned,
就吉他而言，
you've got four fingers on this hand,
你有四个手指在这只手上，
you don't really use your thumb,
你不使用你的拇指，
some players, some country players do use their thumb
一些乡村演奏家使用他们的拇指，
to kind of reach over and catch some of the lower bass notes,
抓住一些低音音符，
but it's pretty tricky to do that
但这样做相当棘手，
and not really all that effective,
而且并不是很有效，
so we're gonna go ahead and bring that wrist down,
所以我们继续，把手腕降低，
and put this hand out,
把这个手放在外面，
like such,
就像这样，
you want make sure,
你想要的确保，
you want to make sure that there's air space right here,
确保这里有空间，
you don't want your wrist to be way up like this,
你不想让你的手腕像这样抬起来，
or gripping the guitar very hard like that,
或者像那样用力握住吉他，
needs to be down a little bit,
需要稍微往下一点，
got a little bit of air space in between there.
中间留出一点空间。
Now let's put our first finger on the first fret,
现在，让我们把食指放在第一个品格上，
okay, where do we put our finger,
好的，我们把手指放在哪里，
well, anywhere between here and here is fair game,
从这里到这里的任何地方都是可以的，
but having said that,
但话虽如此，
right up behind the fret,
在品丝的后面，
is the easiest place to press it down with
是按下它最容易的地方，
and you get them best sound from it,
你就会得到来自它最好的声音，
not on the fret,
不是在品丝上面，
a lot of folks think you might put your finger on the fret,
很多人认为你可能会把你的手指放在品丝上，
not at all,
一点也不，
that gets this kind of funky muted sound is not quite what you're going for,
这种奇怪的静音不是你想要的，
you want to be hugging up right behind that fret.
你想要紧贴在品丝后面。
Okay, ready, we're on the first string,
好的，准备，我们在第一根弦上，
with our first finger,
用我们的食指，
we're gonna pick over here,
我们将在这里拨片，
we're [] our hand,
我们[]我们的手，
and we do this first thing,
我们先做这个，
you ready,
你准备好了吗，
let's play it together.
让我们一起演奏。
Do it again.
再来一次。
That's with our first finger,
这是我们的食指，
now your first finger is going to cover anything that happens on any of the strings,
现在你的食指将覆盖任何弦上发生的任何事情，
in this first fret.
在这第一个品格中。
Your second finger is going to cover anything that happens on any of the strings on the second fret,
你的中指将覆盖第二个品格任何弦上发生的任何事情，
let's try second finger,
让我们试一试中指，
so we released the first finger and put our second finger down here.
所以我们松开食指，把中指放在这里。
Okay, now let's try the third,
好的，现在让我们试试无名指，
so we put third down nice and strong,
所以我们把食指有力地放下来，
release the others up,
把其他放开，
now some of you may be getting a buzzing sort of a sound,
现在你们中的一些人可能会听到嗡嗡声，
kind of like this,
类似这样，
if your fingers aren't strong enough
如果你们的手指不够强壮，
to get good contact with that string to that fret board
不能很好地接触音板上的那根弦，
you kind of end up with this buzzy sound,
最后就会听到这种嗡嗡的声音，
all that's telling you is,
这就是说，
you're not making a good enough contact,
你没有进行足够好的接触，
to make sure that fingers hung up right close back behind that fret,
确保手指紧靠在品丝的后面，
that's the easiest place to put it down,
这是最容易按下的地方，
and there you wanna make sure you get a nice good clear sound.
你要确保你得到一个好的，清晰的声音。
Okay, now let's do pinky,
好的，现在让我们来看看小指，
pinky is going to be the weakest of all of your fingers,
小指是你所有手指中最弱的，
so you're gonna really have to put it down strong.
所以你要把很有力的放下它。
Let's try the pinky,
让我们试试小指，
very good,
非常好，
you want to make sure that,
你要确保，
your hand is not way up here like this,
你的手不会像这样放在这里，
all off centered with your fingers kind of aimed up this way,
手指集中像这样，
you want that wrist down open up those fingers,
你想让手腕向下，张开手指，
I bring it out like that where each finger is covering a fret,
我把它拿出来，每个手指覆盖一个品丝，
a lot of players will come at it like this,
很多演奏者会这样做，
and then when they have to use something in that third or fourth fret,
然后当他们必须在第三或第四个品格中使用一些东西时，
they have to open up their fingers,
他们必须张开手指，
now your hand may not be used to staying out in apart like that,
现在你的手可能不习惯像这样呆在外面，
and unfortunately with guitar playing,
不幸的是，在弹吉他的时候，
you're gonna be doing this position an awful lot,
你会经常做这个姿势，
so eventually it will get more and more comfortable to you,
所以最终它会让你越来越舒服，
it may even be,
甚至可能是，
you know physically impossible for you to move your fingers very apart right now,
现在你的手指不可能非常分开，
your fingers will limber up
你的手指会变得柔软，
as you do it just like if you would be stretching and doing stretching exercises,
在你做伸展练习的时候，
they get more and more flexible, the more that you do it.
你做得越多，手指就会变得越来越灵活。
Let's try this one more time,
让我们再试一次，
we're gonna be on that first string first fret,
我们将在第一根弦上，第一品格，
here we go, let's play this note.
我们开始吧，让我们弹奏这个音符。
Second finger, second fret,
中指，第二个品格，
you want to make sure using your fingertips
你要确保使用你的指尖，
not the flat of your fingers like that,
而不是像这样手指[平的地方]，
you don't want to be doing this,
你不想这样做，
that works real good on the first string,
这在第一根弦上效果很好，
but unfortunately doesn't work very good on the other strings,
但不幸的是，在其他弦上效果不是很好，
so you always want to make sure that your fingers are using the tips.
所以你总是确保你的手指使用指尖。
So we did first, we did second,
所以我们演奏了第一个，演奏了第二个，
here comes third,
这是第三个，
and now we do fourth.
现在我们演奏第四个。
Let's do that one more time.
让我们再来一次。
First, second, third, fourth.
第一个，第二个，第三个，第四个。
Now what should your thumb be doing back here,
现在你的拇指应该在后面做什么，
well I don't really care what your thumb is doing back there,
好的，我不在乎你的拇指在后面做什么，
the only problem is your thumb is attached to your wrist,
唯一的问题是你的拇指附属在你的手腕上，
and I do care about where your wrist is at,
我确实关心你的手腕在哪里，
if your wrist gets too high,
如果你的手腕变得太高，
you end up using the wrong kind of muscles
你最终会使用错误的肌肉类型，
and it doesn't work very well for playing guitar,
它不太适合弹吉他，
you want to make sure that wrist is low,
你要确保手腕是低的，
you want to use your fine motor skills,
你要使用你的精细运动技能，
your little muscles in your fingers,
你手指上的小肌肉，
and bring that down
然后把它放下来，
and so you don't want your thumb way up here like that,
所以你不想让你的拇指像这样升到这里，
it's not a hook,
这不是一个钩子，
you're not hanging your hand on your guitar,
你不会把你的手挂在你的吉他上，
you're gonna bring it back a little bit,
你会把它带回来，
seem to like that.
看起来有点像这样。
Okay, let's talk about tablature,
好的，让我们来谈谈吉他谱，
tablature is a notations that guitars use
吉他谱是吉他使用的一种记号，
to show which fret and which finger needs to be played
用来显示需要哪个品丝和哪个手指演奏，
at any particular time,
在任何时间，
it's not really music notation,
它不是真正的乐谱，
we'll talk about music notation in a minute,
我们会马上讨论乐谱，
this is called tablature,
这被称为吉他谱，
and it's something strictly for guitarists to use it,
这是吉他手必须使用的东西，
it really helps you visualize what fingers you need to place where.
它帮助你直观地知道你需要把哪些手指放在哪里。
So if you can look at your book's figure one,
所以，如果看一下书上的图一，
is a line of tablature
是一个吉他谱，
and let me just explain how that is,
让我来解释一下，
those six lines represented there correspond to the six strings on your instrument,
那六条线对应于乐器上的六根弦，
going in reverse order,
以相反的顺序，
so the top string is actually, the top line is actually your first string,
所以最上面的线是你的第一根弦，
then it goes down to the six string.
然后它向下到六弦。
In figure 2, where they put some numbers on it,
在图 2 中，它们把一些数字放在上面，
and this is they're telling you,
这就是它们想告诉你，
what they're trying to tell you there is
想要告诉你的是，
where to put your fingers,
你可以把手指放在哪里，
what fret do you need to put your fingers on.
你需要把手指放在哪个品丝上。
Okay, so the first notation there you see a little one right up at the top,
好的，第一个符号，你在最上面看到的，
that's telling you on that first string,
它告诉你第一根弦上，
they want you to put your first finger,
想让你把食指放到上面，
and play that note.
然后弹出那个音符。
Okay, the next one after that is a 3,
好的，后面的下一个是 3 ，
but it's still on the first string,
但它仍然在第一根弦上，
so that means you put your third finger,
这意味着你把无名指放在上面，
still on that first string right after that the next note,
仍然在第一根弦上，紧接着下一个音符，
after that it skips down you'll notice to the second string,
之后它跳到第二根弦，
still the third finger though,
仍然是无名指，
that's what that 3 is telling you.
这是 3 告诉你的。
So if I play just those three notes,
所以，如果我只演奏这三个音符，
it would be like this,
就会像这个，
first finger first fret,
食指，第一品，
third finger on that first string,
无名指在第一根弦上，
third finger on that second string,
无名指放在第二根弦上，
you'll notice a little bit further on in that figure 2 exercise,
你会注意到在这个图 2 的后面，
there's a 0,
有一个 0 ，
what 0 is telling you is they want you to play that string,
0 告诉你想要你演奏那根弦，
the second string is the one that it's on open.
第二根弦，它是打开的。
So I'm not fretting any fret at all,
所以我不按任何品丝，
I'm just playing it open.
我只是弹奏开放的。
Now, it's pretty easy when you get the hang of it to read this,
现在，当你掌握了它的诀窍时，它就相当容易阅读了，
even though it looks a little confusing right now,
尽管它现在看起来有点令人困惑，
after you do it a little bit,
但在你做了一点之后，
you kind of see how it goes,
你会看到它是如何进行的，
so if I was to play figure 2,
所以如果我演奏图 2 ，
it would be,
它就会是，
like this first finger, first string,
食指第一根弦，
third finger first string.
无名指第一根弦，
third finger, second string,
无名指，第二根弦，
second finger on the third string,
中指在第三根弦上，
first finger, second string,
食指，第二根弦，
now here comes the open strings
现在是开放的弦，
and open second string and an open first string.
开放的第二根弦和开放的第一根弦。
Now, if you look down to figure 3,
现在，如果你往下看图 3 ，
figure 3 represents how a chord would look,
图 3 代表和弦的外观，
all of these numbers stacked upon each other
所有这些数字堆叠在一起，
are telling you to play all the strings at the same time.
告诉你要同时演奏所有的弦。
Okay, so let's look on what's happening on each of these strings,
好，让我们看看在每根弦上发生了什么，
on the first and second string, you have 0s,
在第一个和第二个弦上，你有 0 ，
so that means those are both open,
这意味着这两个都是开放的，
on the third string, it has a 1 there,
在第三根弦上，它有一个 1 ，
that means you put your first finger down on that first fret,
这意味着你把食指放在第一品上，
on the fourth string and the fifth string, there are 2s,
在第四根弦和第五根弦上，是 2 ，
which means that both the second, on the second fret, on both of those strings are being played
这意味着这两个弦上都是演奏第二品，
and the last one at the bottom is 0,
底部的最后一个是 0 ，
so that means that's open as well,
这意味着它也是开放的，
so if I play all of those together,
如果我把所有这些都放在一起演奏，
comes out to be a chord,
结果就是和弦，
an E chord, you'll learn about that later.
E 和弦，你会在后面学到。
That's how a chord would look in tablature.
这就是和弦在吉他谱上的样子。
Now we're going to talk about some finger exercises,
现在我们要讨论一些手指练习，
let's review,
让我们回顾一下，
on our right hand we used our pick
我们在右手上使用拨片，
and we're going to start doing a picking pattern now.
现在我们将开始一个拨片模式。
Okay, so I want you just on that first string,
好的，所以我希望你只在第一个弦上，
I want you to go a down stroke with your pick,
我希望你用你的拨片来一个向下的拨动，
and then I want you to do an up stroke with your pick.
然后用你的拨片做一个向上的拨动。
Then, let's do it down again, and up again.
那么，让我们再来一次向下，一次向上。
Let's try that again, we're gonna go down up down up.
我们再试一次，我们要下上下上。
Are you ready on the first string?
你在第一根弦准备好了吗？
Let's go, down up down up.
让我们开始，下上下上。
Very good
很好，
and that's the first string,
这是第一根弦，
what's the name of that first string,
第一根弦叫什么名字，
remember that that a E string,
记得吗，它是 E 弦，
let's do it, now we're going to do it on the B string, the second string,
我们现在要做的是 B 弦，第二根弦，
we're going to do the same thing.
我们要做同样的事情。
Are you ready?
准备好了吗？
Down up, down up,
下上，下上，
remember be bracing your pinky on your sound board.
记得在你的声板上支撑你的小指。
Let's try the third string, the G,
让我们试试第三根弦， G ，
here we go, down up, down up,
我们开始，下上，下上，
you wanna go for a good steady rhythm,
你想要一个好的稳定的节奏，
go as slow as you need to go to get a good steady,
尽可能地慢，因为你需要去得到一个好的稳定，
the idea is control, not speed,
想法是控制，而不是速度，
if I can get you control,
如果我能让你控制，
then we can get faster but don't try and be speedy right here,
那么我们可以变得更快，但不要试图在这里太快，
now it's not the time for it,
现在不是时候，
you want to get your hands in control,
你想要控制你的手，
you want your hands to be able do what your brain is telling them to do,
你想让你的手能够做你的大脑告诉它们做的事情，
we are laying a good foundation with all this.
我们正在为这一切奠定良好的基础。
Okay, in the first finger exercise, you see,
好的，在你看的第一个手指练习中，
we have the tablature line there
我们吉他谱线，
and we're gonna do down up down up with our right hand,
我们用右手下上，下上，
but we're going to put our first finger on this first fret, on the first string,
我们要把食指放在第一品，第一根弦上，
so it'll actually end up we'll be playing that four times down up down up,
所以我们将演奏四次，下上，下上，
and then we move to the second finger,
然后我们转到中指，
and we do the same thing,
我们做同样的事情，
then we do the third finger and the fourth
然后我们转到无名指和小指，
and back down,
然后倒退，
so if I play that,
所以如果我弹这个，
I'll play it nice and slow,
我会弹得很好，很慢，
you try and play with me,
你试着跟着我弹，
first finger first fret on the first string
食指，第一品在第一根弦上，
and we're gonna go down up down up nice and evenly,
我们将下上下上，均匀的，
you're ready, let's play.
你准备好了吗，让我们开始。
Down up down up,
下上下上，
now your second finger put him on the second fret,
现在你的中指，把他放在第二品上，
here we go, down up down up,
我们开始，下上下上，
now your third finger on the third fret,
现在你的无名指放在第三品上，
down up down up,
下上下上，
your fourth finger, now your pinky stretching way out there,
你的第四个手指，你的小指伸展到那里，
up down up,
上下上，
now back to the third down up down up
现在回到第三个，下上，下上，
second, there you go and first.
第二个，继续，第一个。
Now this may be a little tricky at first to do,
一开始这可能有点棘手，
everybody thinks they know how to control their fingers
每个人都认为他们知道如何控制他们的手指，
until you start playing guitar,
直到你开始弹吉他，
then you realize that you don't know your brain really doesn't tell your pinky to move independently of the others very often,
然后你意识到你不知道你的大脑不知道你的小指经常独立于其他手指移动，
so we have to kind of train our fingers to do what we need them to do.
所以我们必须训练我们的手指去做我们需要它们做的事情。
Let's do the exercise one more time a little bit faster,
让我们再快一点做一次练习，
try and be steady,
试着稳一点，
you ready, here we go, let's play,
准备好了吗，我们开始吧，我们演奏，
up down up,
下上下，
second finger with no breaks in between right from one to the other,
中指，从一个手指到另一个手指之间没有任何中断，
third finger, fourth finger,
无名指，小指，
now down up down,
现在下上下，
back to third,
回到第三个，
you're doing great,
你做得很好，
here comes second nice and steady,
第二个，好且稳定，
back to first.
回到第一个。
There you go,
好了，
now, we did that on the first string, the E string,
现在，我们在第一根弦上， E 弦，
now we're going to go to the second string, the B string
现在我们要去第二根弦， B 弦，
and let's try that one more time,
让我们再试一次，
this is still exercise number one,
这仍然是练习一，
we're just gonna do it on the second string now.
我们现在要在第二根弦上做。
Ready, play.
准备，弹。
Second finger now,
现在是中指，
make sure you're not getting any buzzes,
确保你没有得到任何嗡嗡声，
puts a lot of pressure on those fingers,
对这些手指施加大的压力，
here comes fourth pinky,
现在到小指，
back to third now,
现在回到无名指，
second finger,
中指，
and first finger,
食指，
very good, very good,
非常好，非常好，
now probably right about now,
现在可能就是现在，
your fingers are getting a little sore,
你的手指有点疼，
which is what happens right about now,
这就是现在发生的情况，
because your fingers aren't used to doing that,
因为你的手指不习惯这样做，
make sure using your fingertips,
确保使用你的指尖，
and your finger, the flesh running your fingertips will tough enough,
你的手指，你的指尖上的肌肉将足够坚韧，
at this stage of the game,
在当前这个阶段，
when you're practicing,
当你练习的时候，
just play until your fingers start hurting,
直到你的手指开始疼痛，
once they start hurting, just back off from it for a while,
它们开始疼的时候，离开一段时间，
there's no advantage to playing through the pain or anything like that,
在疼痛中演奏，没有什么好处，
just just back off from it come back on a few hours later,
只是离开它，几个小时后回来，
a little bit later on the night,
晚上再回来，
give your fingers a chance
给你的手指机会，
to heal up a little bit and toughen up a little bit,
让它愈合一点，变硬一点，
you'll find within about a week,
你会在大约一周内发现，
they'll be nice and strong
它们会很好，很强壮，
to be able to do what you need to do.
能够做你需要做的事情。
Let's go down to exercise number two,
现在让我们去做第二个练习，
now instead of going down up down up,
现在不是下上下上，
we're just going to go down up,
我们只是下上，
so instead of four beats, we've reduced it down to two.
所以我们把它从四个节拍减少到两个。
Let's go to the third string now,
让我们来第三根弦，
remember the name of that third string, G, here we go.
记得第三根弦的名字， G ，我们开始。
First finger, third string, good bracing,
食指，第三根弦，很好的支撑，
here we go,
我们开始，
a little bit faster, down up,
稍微快一点，下上，
now the second string, second finger, excuse me, down up,
现在第二根弦，中指，抱歉，下上，
third finger, fourth finger,
无名指，小指，
back to third,
回到无名指，
back to second,
回到中指，
back to first,
回到食指，
now let's try to put them all together
现在让我们试着把它们放在一起，
instead of hesitating in between each one.
而不是在每一个之间犹豫。
Ready, let's try it again,
准备，让我们再试一次，
let's play,
让我们演奏，
oops, sometimes you'll hit the wrong string, just like I did there,
糟糕，有时候你会打错弦，就像我在那里做的那样，
try one more time,
再试一次，
this will be the third third string, the G string,
这将是第三根弦， G 弦，
two beats on each, ready go,
每次两下，准备开始，
next one,
下一个，
third, fourth,
第三个，第四个，
back to third, second, first.
回到第三个，第二个，第一个。
Alright, let's go out to exercise number three,
好的，让我们现在去练习三，
now instead of just doing two beats,
现在不是只弹两次，
we were doing four initially,
我们最初做的是四，
then we are doing two,
然后我们做的是二，
now we're just going to be down to one.
现在我们只剩下一个了。
Okay, let's go back to the first string.
好的，让我们回到第一根弦。
Brace now,
现在准备好，
we're just doing down strokes on all these,
我们只在所有这些向下弹，
so just be down down down down is tried.
所以只要下下下。
Ready, first string, go,
准备，第一根弦，开始，
down, second finger, third finger, fourth finger,
下，中指，无名指，小指，
back to third, second and first.
回到无名指，中指，食指。
You should really do each of these exercises on all the strings,
你应该在所有的弦上做这些练习，
it'll take a little bit of time
这会花一点时间，
and it's pretty tricky at first,
一开始很棘手，
but as you do it more and more,
但随着你做得越来越多，
your fingers will get better,
你的手指会很快变得更好，
very quickly in being accurate on where they need to go,
准确地定位它们需要到达的位置。
it may seem difficult and a little hesitancy right now,
现在看起来可能很困难，有点犹豫，
you may be trying to move your third finger
你可能正在试着移动你的无名指，
and it just takes you a second before you can actually move that third finger,
你需要一秒钟就可以移动无名指，
that's what, that's what these exercises are for,
这就是这些练习的目的，
they're not meant to be great music at this point,
它们不是很好的音乐，
before we can get to making great music,
在我们可以开始创作伟大的音乐之前，
I gotta get this hand, this hand fire in together,
我必须让这只手，这只手齐心协力，
so that's what these exercises are for.
这就是这些练习的目的。
Last two very quickly, exercise number four,
最后两个，非常快，练习四，
we're going to work out finger independence,
我们要解决手指的独立性，
we're gonna go one two first second finger
我们先做一二，食指，中指，
and then first finger to third finger,
然后是食指，无名指，
first finger to fourth finger,
食指到小指，
first to third,
食指到无名指，
first to second,
食指到中指，
so be like one two, one three, one four,
就像一二一三一四，
one three, one two and one,
一三，一二，一，
let's go back to that first string one more time.
让我们再来回到第一弦。
We'll do this one nice and slow.
我们会慢慢地做好这件事。
Ready, play,
准备，演奏，
one, now two, okay,
一，现在二，
then back to one,
然后回到一，
we're going to go one three,
我们要弹一三，
one three
一三，
and back to one,
然后回到一，
we're going to go one four,
我们要弹一四，
one four,
一四，
now we're going to do one three again,
现在我们要再弹一三，
one three,
一三，
one two,
一二，
and then back to one.
然后回到一。
Let's do that one a little bit faster now,
让我们快一点，
ready, play,
准备，演奏，
one two, one three, one four, one three, one two, one,
一二，一三，一四，一三，一二，一，
very good,
很好，
I know that maybe a little bit quick for you right now,
我知道现在对你来说可能有点快，
but do it a couple more days
但再弹几天，
and then you'll be you'll be [] on it.
你就会很[]了。
Okay, the last one exercise,
好的，最后一个练习，
for the last one I want to touch touch on,
我想演示的最后一个，
this works out our pinky,
这需要我们的小指，
we're gonna go four three, four two, four one,
我们要做四三，四二，四一，
then it just does it again,
然后它再做一次，
four three, four two, four one,
四三，四二，四一，
let's do it on a low string,
让我们在一根低弦上做，
let's do it like on the fifth string, that A string,
让我们在第五根弦上做， A 弦，
you ready, nice and slow,
你准备好了吗，慢一点，
ready play,
开始弹，
four three, four two, four one,
四三，四二，四一，
make sure that wrist is down nice and low,
确保手腕向下，
you're bracing you've got your pick fingering alright,
你正在支撑你的拨弦，
ready, go,
准备好了，开始，
try one more time,
再试一次，
four three, four two, four one,
四三，四二，四一，
very good.
很好。
Okay, we're gonna talk about chords now,
好的，现在我们将谈论和弦，
I know you've been waiting for chords this whole lesson,
我知道你整个课程一直在等待和弦，
waiting through all of these finger exercises
等待通过所有这些手指练习，
and now we're finally last where we start to talk about chords,
现在我们终于开始讨论和弦，
which is the stuff you wanted to learn,
这是你想要学的东西，
when you want to learn guitar anyway.
当你想学吉他的时候。
Chords are written in chord blocks,
和弦是以和弦的形式写成的，
it's again, it's a notation that chord that guitarists used to notate chords,
这也是吉他手用来记录和弦的符号，
basically what you see in your book is a blank chord block,
基本上你在书中看到的是一个空白和弦，
basically it's a diagram of a picture of the end of your guitar,
这是一张吉他末端的示意图，
if you can imagine the end of your guitar being like this,
如果你想象你的吉他末端是这样的，
the dark line at the top of the diagram is the nut right here
示意图顶部的黑线就是这里的琴枕，
and then it goes down with each fret,
然后它下降每个品丝，
as you come down the chord diagram,
当你沿着和弦图从上到下，
as you go across from top from side to side horizontally,
当你水平地穿过琴弦时，
you goes across the strings,
你会通过琴弦，
just imagine like it would be a picture of the top of your guitar
想象一下，你的吉他顶部，
going from the strings across like that.
从琴弦上穿过就是这样。
Now the different lines and different circles mean different things,
现在，不同的线和不同的圆圈意味着不同的东西，
so let me just explain those real quick before we get into that,
所以让我快速地解释一下，在我们进入之前，
an open circle,
一个开放的圆圈，
on them, you'll notice on the bottom diagram,
在它们的底部，你会注意到，
it has an open circle over that first string,
在第一根弦上有一个开放的圆圈，
what that is telling you is
它告诉你的是，
to play that string, but it's going to be open,
演奏那根弦，但它将是开放的，
you're not going to be fingering any note with it,
你不会用手指来按任何音符，
let me just like that,
就像这样，
and let's see what's happening on the second string,
让我们看看第二根弦上发生了什么，
you've got a filled in circle on that first fret,
在第一品上有一个填充的圆圈，
that's telling you they want you to put your first finger on that first fret,
告诉你他们想要你把你的食指放在第一品上，
okay and play that note,
好的，演奏这个音符，
so we've got an open one on the first,
所以我们有开放的在第一根弦，
first finger on that second string,
食指在第二根弦，
the third string, we've got another open,
第三根弦，我们有另一个开放的，
then look what's happening on that fourth string,
然后看看在第四根弦上发生了什么，
we've got a filled in circle over the second fret,
我们在第二品上有一个填充的圆圈，
that means put your finger there,
这意味着把你的手指放在那里，
now which finger do you use,
你用哪个手指，
well, the number underneath that filled in circle, that 2 is telling you,
圆圈下面的数字 2 告诉你，
that they want you to use your second finger to do that,
他们希望你用你的中指来做，
the numbers will not always be there,
数字不会总是在那里，
but sometimes they're there,
但有时它们就在那里，
so that 2 is telling you,
所以这个 2 在告诉你，
they want you to use your second finger for that.
他们想让你用你的中指来做。
On the fifth string, we've got our third finger there, on that third fret,
在第五根弦上，我们有无名指在第三品上，
so let's see if we can play all of these together.
所以，让我们看看我们是否可以一起演奏所有这些。
Okay.
好的。
Very good,
很好，
now, you'll notice,
现在，你会注意到，
on the fifth string, we've got an x,
在第五根弦上，我们有一个 x ，
excuse me, on the sixth string, the bottom string, we've got an x,
抱歉，在第六根弦上，最下面的一根弦，我们有一个 x ，
what is that telling you,
这是什么意思，
well, that's telling you not to play that string,
这告诉你们不要演奏那根弦，
some chords are six string chords,
有些和弦是六根弦，
some chords are five string chords,
有些是五根弦，
some chords are four string chords,
有些是四根弦，
this one is a five string cord,
这是一个五根弦的和弦，
the C chord that we're learning now.
这是我们正在学习的 C 和弦。
So we don't play that six string at all,
所以我们根本不演奏第六根弦，
so make sure don't get sloppy and play that six string anyway,
所以要确保不要草率地演奏第六根弦，
that wouldn't be right,
那是不对的，
you're just playing from the fifth string down.
你只是从第五根弦往下弹。
Now you try.
现在你来试试。
You really got to press those fingers down
你要按下你的手指，
in order to get it to sound out right,
才能让它听起来正确，
okay, you're ready to learn your first two chords.
好的，你已经准备好学习你的前两个和弦了。
The first chord is a C chord,
第一个和弦是 C 和弦，
now you notice,
现在你会注意到，
on this diagram,
在这张图上，
it doesn't have anything over that six string,
它没有任何东西在第六根弦上，
sometimes an x will be there
有时那里会有一个 x ，
to tell you not to play that string,
告诉你不要弹那根弦，
sometimes if it doesn't have anything on that string,
如果它没有任何东西在那根弦上，
a filled in circle or an open circle,
一个填充的圆圈或一个开放的圆圈，
it's telling you not to play that string as well,
它也告诉你不要演奏那根弦，
they just give you the ones that you're actually supposed to be playing.
它们只给你应该演奏的琴弦。
Let's try that C chord one more time,
让我们再试一次 C 和弦，
starting at that fifth string,
从第五根弦开始，
we're gonna go through it,
我们将通过它，
each string, one string at a time.
每根弦，一次一根弦。
Ready, starting on the fifth string,
准备好，从第五根弦开始，
third finger, second finger, open, first finger and open.
无名指，中指，开放的，食指，开放的。
Now we're going to play all of them together,
现在我们要把它们都放在一起，
ready to get back up to fifth, fifth string,
准备回到第五根弦，
let loose, we're gonna play them all together,
松开，我们要一起演奏，
ready go,
准备开始，
one more time.
再来一次。
Now, sometimes your chord may sound,
现在，有时你的和弦可能会发出声音，
if you don't have your fingers in the right spot,
如果你没有把手指放在正确的位置，
you kind of get a couple notes that aren't sounding particularly right
你会得到一些听起来不太正确的音符，
or they're buzzing in some in some respect,
或者它们在某些方面发出嗡嗡声，
check your hand position,
检查你的手的位置，
well, this is that C that I was trying to play,
好的，这是看到我试图演奏的 C ，
on that fifth string and it's too far back,
在第五根弦上，它太靠后了，
I've got to move that finger,
我必须移动那根手指，
where it's just hugging up behind that fret,
在那里，它只是靠着品丝后面，
and then it comes out nice and clear.
然后它出来了很好且清晰。
Now, if you don't have good hand strength
现在，如果你没有很好的手的力量，
and that's what we're building up right now,
这是我们现在正在建立的，
it may kind of even though you have your finger right spot,
它可能是一种，即使你的手指正确的地方，
it may come out as kind of a dead note like that,
它可能会像一种死音符那样，
the only difference between this and this,
这和这之间的唯一区别，
is putting my fingers down a little bit stronger,
就是把我的手指往下压一点，
if you notice I didn't move my fingers at all,
如果你注意到我的手指根本没有动，
it's basically how hard I'm pressing it down,
就是我压它的力度有多大，
if you press it down hard enough,
如果你把它压得足够用力，
eventually that chord will open up and [] up,
最终和弦就会[]，
that's a C chord.
这是 C 和弦。
Now the second chord, we're going to learn is a G7 chord,
现在我们要学习的第二个和弦是 G7 和弦，
C is probably the most common chord you're ever gonna find,
C 可能是你会发现的最常见的和弦，
G7 is probably the next common most common chord you're going to play.
G7 可能是下一个最常见的和弦。
Here, let's go through a string by string,
现在，让我们一个弦一个弦来看，
that first string I've got my first finger, on that first fret,
第一根弦，我用的是我的食指在第一品上，
then the second string, third string and the fourth string are all open,
然后第二根弦，第三根弦和第四根弦都是开放的，
that's easy,
那很容易，
now on the fifth string, I've got my second finger
现在在第五根弦上，我有我的中指，
and on the sixth string the lowest string, that E string remember,
在第六根弦上，最低的一根弦，记住 E 弦，
I've got my third finger.
我有我的无名指。
Let's play them all together,
让我们一起来演奏，
now all together.
现在，所有一起。
Very good,
很好，
okay, if you look at exercise number one,
如果你看练习一，
it goes through the C and the G7 chord,
它通过 C 和 G7 和弦，
alternating between the two,
在这两个和弦之间交替，
so let's start with that,
所以让我们从这个开始，
here's the C chord,
这是 C 和弦，
take a second, get all of your fingers in the right spots,
稍等一下，把你所有的手指都放在正确的位置，
and that diamond right there is just telling you that,
那个钻石符号就是告诉你，
you play that C chord and just hold it,
你要演奏那个 C 和弦，然后按住它，
until it's time for the next G7,
直到下一次 G7 的时候，
so let's play that C chord first.
所以我们先演奏那个 C 和弦。
Ready, go.
准备，开始。
Now let's switch over to that G7,
现在让我们切换到 G7 ，
I can move my third and second finger just up a string,
我可以将我的无名指和中指向上移动一根弦，
and I move my first finger down a string
然后我的食指向下移动一根弦，
and I'm there.
我就到了。
Now I go back to the C chord,
现在我回到 C 和弦，
I move those back into place there,
我把它们移回那里，
this one up and I'm at a C chord.
这个向上，我在 C 和弦。
Back to the G7.
回到 G7 。
And now to the C chord.
现在回到 C 和弦。
We better try that one one more time,
我们最好再试一次，
somehow getting all those chords and the fingers together
以某种方式，把所有的和弦和手指放在一起，
and all that takes a little bit of time and effort
所有需要一点时间和努力的事情，
to do that one more time,
再做一次，
start on that C chord.
从那个 C 和弦开始。
Now switch that G7.
现在换到 G7 。
You may have to do it finger by finger
你可能不得不一个手指接一个地做，
or if you can do it all together, that's even better,
或者如果你能一起做，那就更好了，
let's do a G7.
让我们来做 G7 。
Back to the C chord now,
现在回到 C 和弦，
five string chord remember,
记得是五根弦的和弦，
don't play that lowest six string.
不要演奏最低的第六根弦。
Back to G7, all the strings are used on the G7.
回到 G7 ，所有的弦都在 G7 上使用。
And then back to the C.
然后回到 C 。
Take a look at exercise number two.
让我们来看看练习二。
This is called slash notation,
这就是所谓的斜杠记法，
you'll see this quite a bit as a guitar player,
作为一个吉他演奏者，你会经常看到，
there's something we play in quite a bit,
我们演奏的一些东西，
the different slashes,
不同的斜杠，
all that's telling you,
都是在告诉你，
at this stage of the game is
在弹奏的这个阶段，
you're gonna be strumming one strum for each slash that you see,
你将为每个你看到的斜杠弹一个弦，
okay, so let's get our C chord back up again.
好的，所以让我们再来一次 C 和弦。
And let's do exercise number two.
让我们做练习二。
Ready, play.
准备，弹奏。
Three four, the next measure,
三四，下一小节，
one two three four,
一二三四，
now G7, switch over to G7,
现在换到 G7 ，
next measure, one two three four,
下一小节，一二三四，
and back to that C, one two three four.
回到那个 C ，一二三四。
Very good, now take a look at exercise number three,
很好，现在来看练习三，
now we're gonna alternate those chords a little bit quicker,
现在我们要更快地交替这些和弦，
which, as I know it's probably going a little fast for you,
我知道这对你们来说可能有点快，
but let's try it,
但让我们试一试，
you're ready start on that c.
你已经准备好了，从 C 开始。
Let's go.
我们开始。
One two three four,
一二三四，
now to the G7,
现在换到 G7 ，
try not hesitate between each chord.
试着在每个和弦之间不要犹豫。
Back to C.
回到 C 。
G7, here you go.
G7 ，干得好。
Very good,
很好，
that's the C and that's the G7 chord,
这是 C 和弦，这是 G7 和弦，
now may have moved a little fast for you,
现在可能有点快，
may have trouble keeping up at this point,
因为你可能在这点上跟不上，
but after we do it
但在我们做完之后，
and we go through our workshop time here in a minute,
我们马上完成我们的 workshop ，
then you'll be able to knock these out pretty quickly.
然后你就能很快地把它们[敲掉]。
Okay, welcome to get our tips,
好的，欢迎来到我们的吉他技巧，
on this segment, we're going to talk about specific things that have to do with guitar playing,
这一部分，我们将谈论与吉他演奏有关的具体事情，
that aren't necessarily the technique stuff that we've been governed in the other section.
这些事情不一定是我们在其他部分中规定的技术内容。
These are some things these are some items,
这里有一些东西，
that I would suggest you get from the very beginning,
对于新手的建议，
if you're interested in starting to play guitar,
如果你对开始弹吉他感兴趣，
you can pick these up on our website,
你可以在我们的网站上找到这些东西，
or you can also check your local music store.
或者你也可以去当地的音乐商店看看。
First thing we're gonna talk about is
我们要谈论的第一件事是，
one of the most useful things is an electric guitar tuner,
最有用的东西之一是一个电子吉他调音器，
they come in different shapes and sizes,
它们有不同的形状和大小，
this is a pretty standard one,
这是一个非常标准的，
you would plug your guitar
你会插入你的吉他，
and your guitar would have to have a pickup,
你的吉他有一个拾音器，
in either an electric guitar or an acoustic guitar like this one,
无论是电吉他还是声学吉他，
that does have a pickup in it
只要插上拾音器，
and you plug it in and it helps your guitar tune.
你插上它，就能帮助你的吉他调音。
And as you can see,
正如你所看到的，
the tuning is a little bit of a tricky subject,
调音是一个有点棘手的问题，
if you try and do it manually,
如果你试着手动操作，
so electric tuner like this,
像这样的电子调音器，
sometimes you don't even need to pick up,
有时你甚至不需要拿起，
they have microphones in them
里面有麦克风，
and you just play the note
你只需弹奏音符，
and it tells you whether you need to loosen the string or whether you need to tighten the string
它就会告诉你是否需要放松琴弦或是否需要收紧琴弦，
and when you get in, when you get the dot in the middle,
当你得到中间的圆点时，
then you've you're in tune.
你就进入了音调。
Another thing I would suggest you get right from the very beginning,
还有一件事我建议你从一开始就做好，
is a string winder,
是一个琴弦缠绕器，
a little thing like this probably just cost a buck or two,
像这样的小东西可能只需要一到两美元，
when you're changing strings,
当你换弦的时候，
this is a lifesaver,
这是一个救命稻草，
because you'll be winding and winding these strings all day long,
因为你将一整天都在缠绕这些弦，
if you don't have a string winder,
如果你没有一个琴弦缠绕器，
so it's well worth the buck and a half to get one of these.
所以花 1.5 美元买一个是非常值得的。
Next thing I would suggest is a case,
下一件事我建议是一个盒子，
some of you may have cases that had come with your guitar,
你们中的一些人可能有你的吉他附带的盒子，
a lot of guitars don't come with cases,
很多吉他不是随盒子一起来的，
they just come in a box shipping container,
它们只是装在一个箱子里，
so you don't want to use that as your case,
所以你不想把它作为你的盒子，
it's good for you to go ahead and get a case,
现在你可以去拿一个盒子，
now there's three different types,
有三种不同的类型，
you can get a hardwood case,
你可以得到一个硬木盒子，
which that's as strong as you can get,
它是你能得到的最坚固的盒子，
and that's maybe a little bit more than you're you're wanting to spend,
这可能比你想花的钱多一点，
they're pretty pricey,
它们相当昂贵，
but they do protect your instrument,
但它们确实保护了你的乐器，
the best it can be,
最好的情况是，
that kind of step down from that is called a chipboard case,
从那种叫硬纸板外壳的地方下来，
it's a solid case,
它是一个坚固的外壳，
but it's almost made out of a cardboard,
但它几乎是用硬纸板制成的，
a strong cardboard material,
一种坚固的硬纸板材料，
that's a chipboard case,
这是一个纸板外壳，
that's good for a plugging your guitar around getting in and out of the car that sort of thing,
这对于在进出汽车时给你的吉他是很好的，
the third type of cases,
第三种箱子，
a soft case, a padded case,
软箱，
you put your guitar in this kind of zip it all up,
你把吉他放在这种拉链里，
carried on your back
背在背上，
and carry it out of the car,
从车里拿出来，
it isn't as protective as the hard cases,
它不像硬壳那样有保护作用，
but it does offer some great advantages in portability.
但它在便携性上有一些很大的优势。
Some of the little things that I would suggest you get a metronome,
我建议你买个节拍器，
here's a pretty standard metronome,
这是一个非常标准的节拍器，
they also come in different kinds too,
它们也有不同的种类，
only thing a metronome does is click off a tempo,
节拍器做的唯一一件事就是发出一个节奏，
a good steady tempo,
一个很好的稳定的节奏，
I can speed it up, and slow it down,
我可以加快速度，放慢速度，
they have electronic ones as well.
它们也有电子设备。
Now I encourage you to get there's all kinds of metronomes,
现在我鼓励大家使用各种各样的节拍器，
some of them offer a beep, where it just beeps at you,
有些节拍器会发出嘟嘟声，
other ones you have a click
而另一些节拍器你会发出滴答声，
and I would definitely recommend you get the ones that have a click,
我绝对建议你选择有滴答声的节拍器，
not that has a little beep that goes past,
而不是有嘟嘟声的，
it sounds good, when you're listening to it,
当你听它的时候，它听起来很好听，
but when you actually start playing with one that has a beep,
但当你真正开始演奏有嘟嘟声的节拍器时，
you'll realize it's much better to have one that has a click.
你会意识到有滴答声的节拍器要好得多。
Also I would encourage you to get a music stand,
我也鼓励你买一个音乐支架，
you can get the little wire ones,
你可以买一个小的金属音乐支架，
or you can get a little more sturdy metal music stands,
或者你可以买一个更结实的金属音乐支架，
place for you to put your music,
放你的音乐，
put your resources that you're going off of,
放你要使用的资源，
so you're not just sitting on the couch,
这样你不会坐在沙发上，
looking at it far away at a coffee table or something like that.
远远地看着咖啡桌或类似的东西。
Now, some other things I would suggest you have done with your guitar.
现在，我建议你用你的吉他做一些其他的事情。
Because you want to make sure that your guitar is easy to play,
因为你想确保你的吉他很容易弹，
there's nothing worse than playing a guitar that is just difficult to play,
没有什么比弹一把难弹的吉他更糟糕的了，
it gets you frustrated hurt your fingers
它让你沮丧，弄伤你的手指，
and you end up wanting to chuck the whole thing,
你最终想要扔掉整个东西，
so it's a very good idea to have your guitar setup is what they call it,
所以一个非常好的主意是让你的吉他设置，
have a setup done on your guitar,
在你的吉他上做一个设置，
what they what they do is,
他们所做的是，
they look at your guitar
他们看着你的吉他，
and they look and make sure that your whether your neck is straight,
他们检查确保你的琴颈是直的，
you can do a visual check of that yourself at home
你可以在家里进行视觉检查，
by just kind of looking down the neck of your guitar,
通过检查你的吉他琴颈，
and making sure it's pretty straight,
并确保它是直的，
you don't want it bowing in or bowing back out again.
你不会想让它弯向里面或弯向外面。
And they can adjust your guitar through a metal raw,
他们可以通过一个金属材质来调整你的吉他，
that's actually inside of your sound hole here,
这个金属材质就在你的音孔里，
it's called a truss rod,
它叫做 truss rod ，
so it can be adjusted,
所以它可以调整，
its not that big of a deal at all.
这根本不是什么大不了的事。
The other thing that you want to check on your guitar is the bridge,
另一件事，你想检查你的吉他是琴桥，
your bridge is this right here,
你的琴桥在这里，
remember we talked about,
记得我们说过，
that you want to make sure there's no gaps between it and the sound board,
你要确保它和声板之间没有缝隙，
there should be no gaps,
这里不应该有缝隙，
if there is gaps,
如果有缝隙，
that means it's pulling up
这意味着它正在上升，
and that's not good news.
这不是好消息。
You also want to have adjusted
你也想调整一下，
and this is part of a set up job, is your action,
这是设置工作的一部分，是你的弦高，
what action is the distance of the strings from the fret board,
弦高是弦到音板的距离，
the higher this is, the wider that action is,
这个更高，弦高越宽，
the more difficult that guitar is going to be able to play,
吉他就越难弹，
the closer that is to these frets,
越接近这些品丝，
the easier it's going to be able to play,
就越容易演奏，
if your guitar is hard and difficult to finger
如果你的吉他很难指弹，
and get those notes down without buzzing,
音符不发出嗡嗡声，
have your action checked,
检查你的弦高，
that's probably one of the best things you could do.
这可能是你能做的最好的事情之一。
How do you how should you take care of your guitar,
你应该如何保管好你的吉他，
well, just for just for a second, let's talk about that,
稍等一下，我们来谈谈这个问题，
you don't want to get your guitar too hot,
你不会想把你的吉他太热，
you don't want you to get your guitar too cold,
你不想让你的吉他太冷，
your guitar really is just wood and glue
你的吉他真的只是木头和胶水，
and so if you get this thing too hot,
所以如果你把这个东西弄得太热，
it starts warping and coming undone,
它开始弯曲和松动，
I can put a heat lamp on this bridge
我可以在这个琴桥上放一个加热灯，
and in about five minutes, it peels right up,
大约五分钟后，它就会剥离，
so it really is just wooden glue,
所以它实际上只是木胶，
so you want to make sure you don't do stupid things,
所以你要确保你不会做愚蠢的事情，
like take your guitar in the car in the mall in the middle of summertime,
比如夏天把吉他带到商场里的车里，
that temperature inside your car is probably going to get about 150 degrees at least,
车内的温度可能会达到至少 150 华氏度，
that's well enough to do pretty serious damage to your guitar,
足以对你的吉他造成相当严重的损坏，
so you just want to be real careful with that,
所以你需要非常小心，
it can be hot, but not really hot,
它可能很热，但不是很热，
also, you don't want to get your guitar super cold
你也不会想让你的吉他变得非常冷，
or change temperature really fast,
或者改变温度太快，
it's in the middle of winter,
因为现在是隆冬，
your guitar has been out in the car,
你的吉他一直在车里，
it's well below freezing,
温度远低于零度，
you bring it in whip it out,
你把它拿进来，把它拿出来，
you're going to practice like like I said you should,
你要像我说的那样练习，
that's great,
这很好，
but you set your guitar next to a heater vent,
但你把吉他放在加热器通风口旁边，
that would be bad,
那会很糟糕，
your guitar ever so slightly expands and contracts,
你的吉他略微膨胀和收缩，
and it would crack the finish on top of your guitar,
它会在你的吉他顶部破裂，
it won't affect how it's going to sound,
这不会影响它的声音，
but it's not going to look very pretty, from then on,
但它从那时看起来不会很漂亮，
and there's once you crack your finish,
一旦开始破裂，
there's no going back,
就没有回头路了，
it's like cracking a windshield on a car.
就像打破汽车的挡风玻璃一样。
Last thing,
最后一件事，
you want to be careful not to set anything on top of your guitar,
你要小心，不要把任何东西放在你的吉他上面，
even when you put it in the case,
即使当你把它放在盒子里的时候，
you don't want to put your [] on top of your guitar
你也不想把你的[]放在你的吉他上面，
or put any weight on it down this way,
或者以这种方式放在上面，
there's just not any bracing that way,
没有任何支撑，
and it could crack,
它可能会破坏，
those are just some tips on caring for your instrument
这些只是一些关于照顾你的乐器的小贴士，
and knowing what to look for
知道应该寻找什么，
and some things you should buy at the very beginning.
以及一些你一开始应该买的东西。
Alright, here's your assignment for this session,
好的，这是这节课的作业，
we've done what we've covered a lot of ground,
我们已经完成了很多内容，
but here's what you need to do
但这是你们需要做的，
in order to move on for the next session.
为了继续下一节课。
Do all of the finger exercises in your book on all of the strings
在书中的所有弦上做所有的手指练习，
to toughen up your fingers
以锻炼你的手指，
and also to build motor skill development and control.
同时也建立运动技能的发展和控制。
Second thing you need to do memorize the names of your strings.
第二件你需要做的事情是记住你的弦的名字。
Third thing you need to do practice that C and G7 chord
第三，你需要做的第三件事是练习 C 和 G7 和弦，
and the exercises that are within,
其中的联系，
each note should sound out clearly
每个音符应该听起来很清楚，
and try not to hesitate when you're changing chords,
当你改变和弦时，尽量不要犹豫，
if you do all of these things,
如果你做了所有这些事情，
and practice them faithfully over the next coming days,
在接下来的几天里忠实地练习它们，
you will be ready for the next level
你就可以为下一级做好准备，
and I'm going to help you practice,
我会帮你练习，
when we get to the workshop time,
当我们到了 workshop 时间，
I'll see you there.
我会在那里见你。
Okay, welcome to the guitar workshop time,
好的，欢迎来到吉他 workshop 时间，
this is this is the portion where we get to practice together,
这是我们一起练习的部分，
first thing we do before we practice,
第一件事情，在我们开始练习之前，
wheedle hand stretching exercise,
手部伸展练习，
so I want you to get your hands,
所以我想让你们把手放好，
put a fingertip to fingertip,
把指尖放在指尖上，
start pressing down,
开始向下按，
we're stretching out these muscles,
我们是在伸展这些肌肉，
you're not trying to break your fingers,
你不是想折断你的手指，
now, you're just trying to stretch them down,
现在，你只是试着把它们向下拉伸，
last thing to come down as your palm,
最后一样东西是你的手掌，
then your palm comes up,
然后你的手掌向上，
stretch these out here.
把这些伸展开。
Can you feel the difference,
你能感觉到不同之处吗，
can you feel those muscles stretching out in there,
你能感觉到那些伸展的肌肉吗，
that's a good way to get your hands warm
这是一个让你的手变暖的好方法，
before we get ready to play.
在我们准备演奏之前。
Now, let's do these finger exercises,
现在，让我们来做手指练习，
that we talked about on your page,
我们在页面上讨论过的，
we start out with the first finger exercise,
我们从第一个手指练习开始，
number one, remember we're going down up down up with our hand, right hand
第一个，记得我们要用手下上下上，
and we're going to go one two three four, three two one with our left hand,
我们要用左手演奏一二三四，三二一，
we will do it slowly at first
我们会先做得慢一点，
and then we'll play one time a little bit faster.
然后再一次快一点。
Here we go, down up down up with our pick,
我们开始，使用我们的拨片下上下上，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
first finger,
食指，
second finger,
中指，
third finger,
无名指，
fourth finger,
小指，
back third,
回到无名指，
second,
中指，
first,
食指，
let's do that again,
我们再做一次，
go back up to second,
继续，
second,
中指，
there you go,
就这样，
third,
无名指，
fourth,
小指，
bracing your hand slow and steady,
缓慢而稳定地支撑你的手，
make sure your fingers are doing exactly what they need to be doing.
确保你的手指在做它们需要做的事情。
Very good,
很好，
now we're gonna do that one just a little bit slightly faster,
现在我们要稍微快一点，
see if you can keep up.
看看你能不能跟上。
Ready, go.
准备，开始。
Your fingers should be moving just like a machine,
你的手指应该像机器一样移动，
back to third,
回到无名指，
fingers that aren't being used
没有在使用的手指
should be just hovering right above the fret board where they need to go,
应该悬停在它们要去的音板的正上方，
slow even strokes,
慢拨弦，
try one more time, a little bit faster,
再试一次，稍微快一点，
ready, go.
准备，开始。
Very good, let's go to the second string,
很好，让我们来到第二个弦，
what's the name of that second string, that's your B string,
第二根弦叫什么，你的 B 弦，
try here we go,
试一试，
ready, go.
准备，开始。
Very good, now stood on the third string.
非常好，现在到第三根弦上。
Ready, play.
准备，演奏。
Fourth string,
第四根弦，
nice and even and steady
好且平稳，
you're doing great,
你做得很好，
keep those fingers down.
保持你的手指放在下面。
Fifth string, try it,
第五根弦，试一下，
ready go,
准备，开始，
back first.
回到食指。
Last string, low E string
最后一根弦，低 E 弦，
and ready play,
准备，弹奏，
keep that wrist down,
保持手腕向下，
make sure you're bracing on that right hand,
确保你在右手支撑，
good pick position,
好的拨片位置，
a little bit tough to push down,
有点难往下推，
you may be buzzing on a couple of these,
你可能在这些东西上嗡嗡作响，
maybe hugging up right behind that fret,
也许就靠在那个品丝后面，
here we go.
我们开始。
very good, that's exercise number one,
非常好，这是练习一，
let's do exercise number two.
我们做练习二。
Now instead of going down up down up,
现在不是下上下上，
we're just gonna go down up,
我们要做的是下上，
okay, let's go back to our first string again.
好的，让我们再回到第一根弦上。
Ready, go,
准备，开始，
down up down up,
下上，下上，
third finger,
无名指，
second string, go,
第二根弦，开始，
third string, a bit faster now,
第三根弦，现在快一点，
fourth string, a little bit faster, even still,
第四根弦，再快一点，
here you go, try keep up, fifth string,
干得好，跟上，第五根弦，
last one six string, go.
最后一根，第六根弦开始。
Very good, exercise three,
非常好，练习三，
now we're just doing down just one on each,
现在我们只做下，每根弦一次，
okay let's start a little bit slower back on that,
好的，让我们开始慢一点，
well let's go back to that six string,
让我们回到那第六根弦上，
let's start there,
让我们从那里开始，
change it up a little bit.
稍微改变一下。
Ready, go,
准备，开始，
one two three four three two one,
一二三四，三二一，
good, next string go,
好的，下一根弦开始，
third string go,
第三根弦开始，
second string, faster,
第二根弦，速度更快，
there you go, fingers work
手指开始工作，
and first string.
第一根弦。
Good, exercise four,
好的，练习四，
remember goes one two, one three, one four,
记得一二，一三，一四，
first string, ready, go,
第一根弦，准备，开始，
one two, one three, one four, one three, one two one,
一二，一三，一四，一三，一二一，
let's go to third string,
让我们进入第三根弦，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
one two, one three, one four, one three, one two one.
一二，一三，一四，一三，一二一。
Skip over the fifth string,
跳到第五根弦，
Last exercise there believe it's your fifth exercise there,
最后一个练习相信这是你的第五个练习，
four three, four two, four one,
四三，四二，四一，
let's touch on that first string,
让我们从第一根弦开始，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
four three, four two, four one,
四三，四二，四一，
second string, four three, four two, four one,
第二根弦，四三，四二，四一，
third string.
第三根弦。
Very good little bit faster,
很好，快一点，
fourth string,
第四根弦，
fifth string, faster,
第五根弦，快一点，
six string, faster still.
第六根弦，仍然快一点。
Okay, now let's work on our chords,
好的，现在让我们练习和弦，
remember our two chords that we did,
记得我们做的两个和弦，
the C one is the first one,
C 是第一个，
let's make sure we form it right,
让我们确保我们的形式正确，
it's a five string chord,
它是一个五弦和弦，
third finger on that fifth string, third fret,
无名指在第五根弦上，第三品，
second finger, fourth string, second fret,
中指，第四根弦，第二品，
the G on the third string is open,
第三根弦上 G 是开放的，
first finger on that second string first fret C,
食指在第二根弦上，第一品， C ，
the last one is open,
最后一个是开放的，
play altogether.
一起弹奏它们。
Now, all at the same time,
现在，所有的都同时，
that's our C chord.
这是我们的 C 和弦，
Let's form our G7 chord,
让我们形成 G7 和弦，
switch our fingers over,
换一下手指，
remember your third and your second finger just need to go up one string set
记住你的无名指和中指只需要向上移动一根弦，
and they're already where they need to be,
它们已经在它们需要的地方，
move that first finger down one string set
把食指向下移动一根弦，
and he's where he needs to be,
他就在他需要的地方，
G7 [] go through, each one note at a time,
G7 ，一次一个音符，
all together.
全部一起。
Alright, now we're gonna jump between those chords,
好的，现在我们要在这两个和弦之间跳跃，
okay, starting an exercise one on the chord examples,
开始一个练习，
starts on the C chord,
从 C 和弦开始，
let's do four counts
让我们做四次计数，
for each one of those notes that you're holding it for.
对你持有的每个音符。
So let's go, ready play,
让我们开始，准备，弹奏，
C chord, one two three,
C 和弦，一二三，
now change that G7 go, two, three,
现在切换到 G7 ，开始，二三，
back to the C now, two three,
现在回到 C ，二三，
G7, two three four
G7 ，二三四，
and back to C.
回到 C 。
Pretty good,
很好，
let's try it,
让我们试一试，
let's speed it up just a little bit,
让我们把速度加快一点，
ready, play,
准备，演奏，
C, one two three,
C 一二三，
G7, two three,
G7 二三，
back to C, two, three,
回到 C ，二三，
G7, two, three,
G7 ，二三，
back to C.
回到 C 。
Great, let's move on to exercise number two,
好的，让我们继续第二个练习，
remember we do a strum for each slash that's on the page,
记得我们对页面上的每个斜杠做一个弦，
remember for a C chord, don't be hitting that low sixth string,
记住 C 和弦，不要敲打低的第六弦，
just five strings on the C chord,
C 和弦上只有五根弦，
ready, let's start nice and slow exercise two,
让我们开始缓慢的练习二，
ready go.
准备，开始。
Slow even strums, one two three,
慢连弹，一二三，
G7 now, switch your fingers over go,
现在 G7 ，把你的手指换过来，
one two three,
一二三，
back to C.
回到 C 。
Pretty good, let's try one more time,
很好，让我们再试一次，
ready, a little bit faster,
准备，更快一点，
this time starting on the C,
这次从 C 开始，
ready,
准备，
here you go here comes out G7, go,
干得好，这是一个 G7 ，开始，
get ready for that C chord,
做好 C 和弦的准备，
be thinking where you put your fingers go.
思考你的手指放在哪里。
Very good, one more time,
很好，再来一次，
a little bit faster,
再快一点，
ready, go.
准备，开始。
Even strums,
[扫弦]，
push down those fingers nice and hard.
用力按下手指。
Very good,
非常好，
let's move on exercise number three,
让我们继续第三个练习，
now we're gonna switch those chords a little bit faster,
现在我们要更快地切换和弦，
we're going to go between the C and the G7,
我们将在 C 和 G7 之间移动，
but only four beats in between each,
但每个之间只有四个拍子，
ready play,
准备，演奏，
C,
C ，
now G7,
现在 G7 ，
back to C,
回到 C ，
G7,
G7 ，
how are you doing,
你还好吗，
you're hanging in there still one more time,
你再坚持一次，
a little bit faster, this time,
再快一点，这次，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
G7,
G7 ，
back to C,
回到 C ，
pretty good, G7,
很不错， G7 ，
C.
C 。
Okay, this will be the last time we do it,
好的，这是我们最后一次这样做，
so really going to kick it up a notch on the speed,
所以要把它的速度提高一个档次，
see if you can keep up,
看看你是否能跟上，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
G7,
G7 ，
back to C,
回到 C ，
back to C.
回到 C 。
Very good, I hope you've learned something this first session,
我希望你在第一次课程上学到了一些东西，
a couple things I want you to think about as you're practicing,
我想让你在练习时思考一些事情，
remember about fifteen minutes or more five out of seven days a week
记住一周七天中有五天十五分钟或更多，
is a good place to start on practicing,
是开始练习的好地方，
you will only improve by the methods effort that you put in it,
只有通过你投入的方法努力才能提高你的水平，
man, I wish I could just tell you the information
伙计，我希望我能告诉你信息，
and you would get it,
你会得到它，
but unfortunately, there's a lot of stuff that you got to do on your end,
但不幸的是，你有很多事情要做，
which is practicing,
那就是练习，
so I encourage you to do that five out of seven days a week,
所以我鼓励你一周七天中的五天去练习，
fifteen minutes or more,
15 分钟或更多，
if you can pull up to thirty minutes five out of seven days a week,
如果你一周七天中有五天能坚持到三十分钟，
that's great,
那就太好了，
doesn't have to be at the same block either,
不需要是相同的时间块，
you can just do a few minutes in the morning,
你也可以早上只做几分钟，
maybe a few minutes at nine,
也许九点的几分钟，
keep working hard at it and I'll see you next time.
继续努力，下次再见。